I'm Kotomi Tachibana, the red color person in charge of Candy Tune.
I don't know what it is about my personality.
I'm a competitive person, and I feel that I hate to lose.
I don't want to compromise on every single thing, and when I decide to do something, I'll do it until I'm satisfied with it.
There are good things and there are also bad things.
I also feel that way.
I've heard from the members that I'm
I'm often told that I'm strange or that I don't communicate well with them.
I often mispronounce things or mishear things,
I don't really want to say it myself, but I feel like I'm a natural,
I don't like to say it, but I am often called a natural.
I'm not convinced.
I didn't think I would be an idol.
I didn't really think I would do it.
I wasn't really thinking about it, but I was thinking about what I couldn't achieve.
things that I couldn't achieve or things that I want to do
I thought that maybe I could make it happen.
I got a decision for a long period of time.
At that time, I was anxious and
I was excited.
I had always loved idols when I was little,
I was also a real TV kid,
I would always watch singing shows,
I would dance in front of the TV all the time while replaying the show. I never learned how to dance, but I wanted to show my family and myself how to dance.
I've never learned to dance, but I had a rule that I wanted to show my family that I was really good at it all day long.
I think that was the best angle for me.
I did it like this.
When I met my mother...
I felt like I could expose everything to her.
The bad times, the good times, the sad times...
Only with my mother...
It's amazing.
I can open up to her about anything.
Even if I don't solve the problem, just by listening to me, I can change my mind and do my best.
The most honest
I show my true colors
My mother is the only one I show my true colors to.
There are many moments when I feel anxious.
I have a lot of moments
I wonder if I'll be successful.
There are a lot of moments when I wonder if I'm going to succeed.
There are a lot of moments when I wonder if I'm going to make it.
I have to work harder, I have to work harder.
I have to work harder, I have to work harder
I have a lot of feelings that I have to work harder.
But I'm also thinking about all the members of Candy Chuu and the people who are involved with us.
and the people who are involved in my work
I really feel that we are working together to improve and do our best.
So I'm going to believe in it and enjoy it.
I'm going to do my best until my debut.
I want to do my best until we make our debut.
I want to make Candy Tune a group that only Candy Tune can do.
I want to make Candytune a group that only Candytune can do.
I want to be loved by people of all ages for a long time.
I don't want to
I don't want to be an idol.
I want to make a career out of being an idol.
I want to change people's lives
I want to move people's hearts.
I've wanted to be that kind of person since I was 6 years old.
I've been thinking about it since I was 6 years old.
I've been playing modern ballet for 10 years.
I'm not very good at public speaking, but I loved to dance and express myself in front of people.
but I loved to dance and express myself in front of people.
I love to dance and express myself in front of people.
I thought I would be someone who could make people happy, or make them happy, or move them.
I thought I would become a person who could make people happy or happy or moved them.
I want to be someone who can proudly say, "I am an idol," which was my dream when I was 6 years old.
I want to deliver such a scene to everyone who supports me from now on.
Candy Tune has pushed me to be the person I am today.
They have helped me a lot.